Guide to the Clive L. DuVal papers, 1960-1994
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 2: Legislative Files, 1966-1992
  - Subseries 2.1 - Congressional Bills, 1966-1992; (68 Boxes)
    - FC - Changes in State Law (Trading Ordinance), SB486, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Ordinance Trading State Law, SB486, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - FC - Denial of Bus License if Tax Arrears, SB487, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Victim Impact Statement, SB488, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Fairfax Board - Election if Vacancy Occurs, SB490, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Water and Sewer Authorities Retirement Plans, SB525, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Housing (Arlington Low and Moderate Income Tenants), SB549, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Raffles Bill (Northern Virginia Builders), SB559, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Retirees $3,000 Deduction, SB585, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - SCC - Collection of Taxes, SB621, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Reorganization of Airports, SB711, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Homestead Exemption - Constitutional Amendment, SJR027, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Pogonia Resolution, SJR97, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - JLARC Study Resolution, SJR178; SB714, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Special Agents - Hazardous Duty Retirement Benefits, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Appraiser (McCloud B. Hodges), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Beverage Container Legislation, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Capital Outlay Projects/Tours, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Claims, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - CLD Budget Requests, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Fairfax County, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Generic Drug Substitution, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - GMU/NVCC Budget Needs, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Heritage Program (Nature Conservancy), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Insurance Law Recodification, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Judges - Clive DuVal, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Legislation, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Metro Defense, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Scenic Rivers, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Senate Finance Committee Issues, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Bills: Special Session, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Unsolicited Commercial Telephone Calls, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Victims of Crime Act, Study CLD Chairman, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Water Resources Research Center, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - James W. Pearson, HB0008, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Father of Anthony Spttswood Colbert, Jr., HB0055, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - J. M. Turner and Co., Inc., HB0076, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Gary L. Marks and Joan D. Marks, HB0103, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - John C. Sample, HB0103, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Claude Woodrow (Woody) Anderson, Jr., HB0106, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Arniel C. Uzel, HB0108, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Escheat, SB002, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Claims Exemption Bills, Limiting Time to Introduce, SB004; HB0368, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Family of David Lee Lovel, SB009, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Gerald G. Wheatley, SB076, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Tax Exemption - High Speed Duplication, SB164, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Victims of Crime Comp. Act, SB251, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Cecil D. Collins, Jr. and Katherine W. Collins, SB253, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Dillon's Rule, SR004, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Arlington County, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Arrowine, McLean, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - "Boatels,", 1987 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Claims Bills, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Claims for Richmond, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Conflict of Interest Bablas, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Democratic Fundraiser, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Drug Abuse in Schools - Task Force (Northern Virginia Action Council), 1987 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Fairfax County, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Falls Church, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - George Mason University, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Income Tax Reduction - Increased Pers. Exemption, etc., 1987 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Northern Virginia Community College (NVCC) - Budget Amendments, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Pesticide Operators - Insurance Problems, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Phosphate Detergent Ban, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - POW License Plates, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Professional Counselors, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Purple Heart License Plate, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Rural Coops TV, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Seniority, Change in Sen. Rules, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Veterans Budget Amendment, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Victims of Crime Act, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Vienna, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Firefighters Bill, HB1611, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Lottery, SB013, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Senate Bill (Lottery), SB369, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - DuVal Co-Sponsored Bills, SB369; SB426; SB428; HB0991, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Senate Bill (Lottery Referendum, SB390, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Senate Bill (Zoning Ordinances), SB399, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - License Plates, POW, SB456, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Health Insurance Plans, SB459, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - License Plates, Purple Heart, SB460, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Income Tax Exemption, SB497, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Leases of State Park Lands, SB498, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Income Tax Reduction - Credit, etc., SB541, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Individual Income Tax Credit, SB541, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Water Supply Revolving Fund, SB553, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Water Revolving Fund, SB553, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Exemption of Marine Resources Commission, SB555, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Alzheimer's Disease Registry, SB560, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Subdivision - Zoning, SB650, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Regional Airport Authority, SB672, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Virginia Airport Authority Amendment, SB672, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Seniority of Senators, SJR038, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Telecommunications Industry, SJR135, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Transportation Needs, SJR148, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Acupuncture Regulation, SJR16, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Absentee Ballots and Emergency, SB7, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Aids, SJR82, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Animal Wardens - Restrictions on Powers, HB929, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Arlington County, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Chesapeake Bay Preservations Act, HB925, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Claims Bills, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Constitutional Convention, SJR22, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - CIT Floor Fight, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Conservation Laws - Code Commission, SB239, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - 1988 Interlock Bill, SB213 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Consumer Finance Bill, HB980, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Court Room Prohibiting the Carrying of Weapons into a Room, SB71, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Exemption to Road Tax on Motor Carriers, SB417, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Falls Church, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Fairfax Secondary Roads / New Constitution Procedures, SB461, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Inspection of Records, SB273, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - George Mason University, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - 1988 Nature Conservancy, SB268 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Neighborhood Assistance Act, SB67 Amendment, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Metro 1988 Floor Fight Anticipation of Senate Floor Amendment Cutting Metro Funds (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Nontidal Wetlands, HB137, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Speed Limit - 65 Miles Per Hour (covers on truckers), 1988 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Unclaimed Project / Retail Merchants, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Vehicular Homicide, HB641, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Liability Insurance, SJR48; SJR120, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Northern Virginia Community College, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Purple Heart, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - EDA/Miller F., 1988 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Retirees Income Tax Deductions, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Disclosure, Fairfax County, SB36, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Agreements with the Commonwealth Transportation Board Route 28, SB439, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Solid Waste Separation, SB160, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Tenants Tax Incentive; Housing Study, SB159, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Toy Firearms Used in Felony, SB214, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Vienna, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Beach/Coastal Control Issues Subcommittee Study, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Beverage Containers/Recycling, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Senator Clive DuVal Emission Testing, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Conservation Easement, HB799, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - Education Governor's Budget Proposal, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - Endangered Plants, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Family Life Proposal, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Food and Beverage Tax All Counties, HB821, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Military in-State Tuition, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Citizens Consumer Council, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Pari-Mutuel Betting, HB900, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Pound Seizure, HB489, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Statute for Religious Freedom, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Senate Finance Committee Amendments, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Statute for Religious Freedom, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Water Project, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Water Resources Center-Budget Amendment, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - WNVT Channel 53, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Retail Sales and Use Tax Exemption (Folder Empty), SB268, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Bills Co-Sponsored by DuVal, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - $3000 Tax Exemption, SB6, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Absentee Ballots, SB7, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Supervisors, Disclosures, etc., SB36, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Neighborhood Assistance Act, SB67, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Prohibiting Weapons in Courtrooms, SB71, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Alternative Tax Rate for Sales of Certain Real Estate, SB159, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Separation of Solid Waste, SB160, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Ignition Interlock Device, SB213, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Look-Alike Firearms, SB214, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Retail Sales and Use Tax Exemption, SB268, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Inspection of Records of Utilities by SCC, SB273, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Exemption to Road Tax on Motor Carriers, SB417, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Transportation Trust Fund Bonds, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Agreements with the Commonwealth Transportation Board, SB439, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Highway Construction and Improvement by Counties, SB461, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Acupuncture Study, SJR16, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Balanced Federal Budget Rescind Constitutional Convention, SJR22, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Liability Insurance Crisis 7, Need for Tort Reform, SJR48, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - AIDS, SJR82, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Crime Victim Compensation, SB618, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Income Tax Surcharge, SB691, undated (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - MC Lean Underground Wiring Small Districts, SB692, undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Vinson Tax Exemption, SB693, undated (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Affordable Housing, SB806, undated (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Transient Occupancy Tax, SB811, undated (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Tax Relief / Elderly Handicapped, SB812, undated (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Gasoline Tax, 5%, SB810, undated (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Patent Act 200th, SJR134, undated (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Non-Tidal Wetlands Study, SJR222, undated (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Abortion Rights, undated (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Adoption / Private Surrogate Parenting, undated (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Aging, undated (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Arbitration, HJR178, undated (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Aids-Bills and Budget Amendments, undated (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Arlington, undated (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Bonding, undated (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Budget Amendments, undated (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Chief Patron Report, undated (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Clean Indoor Air, undated (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - Constitutional Conventions, HJR22, undated (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - C and P / Park Authority, undated (Box 87, Folder 22)
    - Democratic Caucus, undated (Box 87, Folder 23)
    - Education, undated (Box 87, Folder 24)
    - File, 1989 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Affordable Housing, SB806, undated (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Information - Senator DuVal, undated (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Arlington County, undated (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Budget Amendment, undated (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Circuit CT Judgeship Candidates, 1989 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Claims Policy, undated (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Crime Victim Compensation JL ARC, SB618, undated (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Deregulation of Virginia Telephone Companies, undated (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Dulles Toll Road Bonding, SB808, undated (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Fairfax County, undated (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Falls Church, 1988-1989 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Game Preserves, HB1125, undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Gasoline Tax, 5%, SB809, undated (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Gift Lot, HB1721, undated (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Impact Fees, HB1485, undated (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Income Tax, Government Option, SB691; HB1684, undated (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Income Tax Credit, HB1417, undated (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Langley Tax Exemption, SB609, undated (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Lobbyists, 1988-1989 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Local Tax Options, 1988-1989 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Long Wall Mining Bill and Correspondence, undated (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Mammograms, HB1449, undated (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Vepco Multiple Rate Increases, HB1789, undated (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - McLean Underground Wiring / Small Districts Wiring, SB692, undated (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Non-Tidal Wetlands Study, SJR222, undated (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Northern Virginia Community College, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Northern Virginia Regional Park Authority USC and P, undated (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Patent Act 200th, SJR134, undated (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Pesticide Control, 1989 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Record from Taxes, HB1720, undated (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Highway Route 58 in Southern Virginia, HJR172, undated (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Rules Committee, undated (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Recycling of Beverage Containers, 1989 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Smoking Restrictions in Public Places, undated (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Tax Relief / Elderly Handicapped, SB812, undated (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Transient Occupancy Tax, SB811, undated (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Trucks - Large, SJR121, 1989 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Value Engineering, undated (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Veteran's Home Budget Amendment, undated (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Vinson Tax Exemption, undated (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Waste Management, undated (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Air Quality: Vapor-Trapping Gasoline Pumps Nozzles, undated (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Arlington County, undated (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Binding Arbitration / Teachers, undated (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Budget Amendment, undated (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Caller ID (pt 1), SB181, undated (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Caller ID (pt 2), SB181, undated (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Caller ID (pt 3), SB181, undated (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Caller ID (pt 4), SB181, undated (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Fairfax County Legislation Package, undated (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Fairfax County Schools, undated (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Family Life Ed. / Child Issues, undated (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Carry Over Bills, undated (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Langley Tax Exemption, SB609, undated (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Dulles Toll Road / Bonding, SB808, undated (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Fish Ladder Budget Amendment, undated (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - SB809, undated (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Guns, SB727, undated (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - George Mason University (GMU), undated (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Head Injury Budget Amendment, undated (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Health Care Trust Fund, undated (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Homeless Issues Budget Amendment, undated (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Judicial Review Public Assistance, SB437, undated (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Krispy Kreme, undated (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Labor, undated (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - NOVA Grievance, undated (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Pharmacists and Related Issues, undated (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Porsche Claim, undated (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Pound Seizure, HB933, undated (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - Transfer Tax, undated (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Saving and Loans Issues, undated (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Transportation, undated (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Trees - Utilities, undated (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Value Engineering, undated (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Vepco Appeal - Rate Increase, undated (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Veterans Home, undated (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - W and OD Pedestrian Bridge, undated (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - "Cost" Dykes (Changing Group / Fairfax Form of Gov.), undated (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Fair Housing Code, SB474, undated (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Commending David Low, SJ146, undated (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Constitutional Convention, undated (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Dates for Payment of Local Taxe (Fairfax County), SB329, undated (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Fairfax County, undated (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Fairfax County, undated (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Fairfax County: Taxes, Income Option, Vested Rights, etc., undated (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Route 28, Use of Excess Bond Re: Proceeds for Phase 2 of Route 28, SB325, undated (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Work Management Tax, SB119, undated (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Falls Church, undated (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Income Tax Administration, SB326, undated (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - George Mason University (GMU) Senate Resolution No. 1, undated (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Paul W. Timmreck - Northern Virginia Community College, undated (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Local Government May Exempt Recycling Facilities, SB289, undated (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Recycling: State Agencies, SB287, undated (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Retiree Legislative, SB250, undated (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Real Estate Taxes Deferral, SB328, undated (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Recycled Paper, SB288, undated (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Route 28 Tax District, SB170; HB721, undated (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Subdivision Office Site Contribution, SB416, undated (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Landlord/Tenant Act, SB285, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Legislation, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Legislation, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Time Off to Vote, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Senate (CLD Chairman), undated (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Value Engineering, undated (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Vienna, Town of, undated (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Vesting Problems, etc., undated (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Vasquez Case - Violations of His Rights by Arlington Police, undated (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Hampton Road / Northern Virginia Joint Transportation Caucus, undated (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Augmented Estate / Abolishment of Dower, HB808, undated (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Waste Management Subcommittee, SB464, undated (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Stump Dump, HB855, undated (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Governor's Schools, undated (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Proffer Legislation, HB721, undated (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Senate Finance, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Senate Finance, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - JILARC Study on Comm. of Revenue / Filing Tax Returns, SB326, undated (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Vesting/Down Zoning, undated (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Vesting, undated (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Banks and Insurance, HB335, undated (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - 1990 Budget Documents, HB29, ca. 1989 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Executive Budget of the Commonwealth of Virginia 1990-1992, ca. 1989 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Northern Virginia Sub Regional Plan Policy Committee (pt 1), undated (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Northern Virginia Sub Regional Plan Policy Committee (pt 2), undated (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Northern Virginia Sub Regional Plan Policy Committee (pt 3), undated (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Northern Virginia Sub Regional Plan Policy Committee (pt 4), undated (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Northern Virginia Sub Regional Plan Policy Committee (pt 5), undated (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Abortion, undated (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Aging, undated (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Acid Rain, undated (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - AIDS Human Immunodeficiency Viruses, HJR129, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Air Pollution, undated (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Airways Engineering, undated (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Airways Enquire, undated (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Lesson Sampler for Virginia Law and Government, undated (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Telephone Caller ID, SB181, undated (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Real Estate Assessments Limitations on Annual Increase, undated (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Time Off to Vote, SB286, undated (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Local Option Income Tax, SB173, undated (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Acupuncture, SB174, undated (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Commissioners of Revenue, SB326, undated (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Tax Differential, SB180, undated (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Landlord/Tenant Act, SB285, undated (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Recycling: State Agencies, SB287, undated (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Recycled Paper, SB288, undated (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Local Government May Exempt Recycling Facilities, SB289, undated (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Air and Space Museum Attention, SB323, undated (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Route 28 Use of Excess Proceeds for Phase 2 of Route 28, SB325, undated (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Real Estate Cap, 8% CPI, SB327, undated (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Real Estate Taxes Deferral, SB328, undated (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Dates for Payment of Local Taxes, SB329, undated (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Subdivision Off-Site Contributions, SB416, undated (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Fair Housing Code, SB474, undated (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - Commending David Low, SJR146, undated (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - Study Re: Disposal of Major Appliances, SJR87, undated (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - Study on Higher Education in Northern Virginia, SJR90, undated (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - Senate Caucus, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Clive DuVal Bills, undated (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Legislation, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Legislation, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Airport Authority Violation of Noise, SB592, undated (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Arlington County, undated (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Boating Advisory, SB591, undated (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Bottle Bill, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Budget Amendments, undated (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Budget Matters - Governor Wilder vs. Legislative Branch, undated (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - By-Pass, Western, undated (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Chesapeake Bay Act on Regs., undated (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Commending Dr. Davis, SJR215, undated (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Commerce and Labor Committee, Subcommittee 3, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Comp. Board Limiting Appeals, SB879, undated (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Disparity of Education Governor's Commission, undated (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Early Retirement File, undated (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Educational Disparity, Legislation Study of, undated (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Ethanol Program, Elimination of, HB1961, undated (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Fairfax County, 1990-1991 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Fairfax County, 1990-1991 (Box 106, Folder 13)